



■ afun@afun.tw | 🛪 afun.tw | 🖶 afunTW | in chen-ming-yang | 🜬 @afun | 🖪 a_fun

"A Foolish Consistency is the Hobgoblin of Little Minds"

Summary.

Current research assistant in Academic Sinica and Institute of Information Science. With 2+ years of experience in computer vision / deep learning, Interested in learning new technologies and tools to enhance my own workflow. So far, familiar with the development on Ubuntu with tmux, vim, vscode, jupyter, git, docker, etc.

Work Experience _____

Academic Sinica, Institute of Information Science

Taipei, Taiwan

RESEARCH ASSISTANT & RDSS (COMPULSORY MILITARY SERVICE)

Aug. 2016 - PRESENT

- Build up the tracking pipeline from scratch. Cooperate with Biodiversity Research Center, ESSLab. (GitHub)
- · Publish the paper "Artificial intelligence reveals environmental constraints on colour diversity in insects". Cooperate with ESSLab.
- Developed some easy-to-use UI for data annotation by tkinter and PyQt5.
- Designed and have the speech a payment course, Python-Crawling-Tutorial. (datasci, AIA, GitHub)
- Developed a pipeline to discriminate the cyber warrior on PPT.
- Developed a simple dashboard with SB Admin2 to visualize organization data. (datasci)
- Manage lab server over 10+ machines including GPU server and NAS.

Imonology Remote, Taiwan

INTERN & QA ENGINEER

Sep. 2015 - Apr. 2016

· Test the IPCam System in Scrum.

ASUS Central section, Taiwan

Jun. 2012 - Jun. 2013

- INTERN & CAMPUS EXECUTIVE OFFICER
- Storage management and Customer service in the repair center. (part-time)
- Support win8-series product press conference.
- Promoter Support in Information exhibition. (Taichung)
- Support distributor conference

Skills & Interested_

tmux + ssh on Ubuntu > jupyter (test / vis) > *.py + *.sh + pipenv or Dockerfile (deploy)

DEVELOPMENT

3+ years **Ubuntu**, Used in daily life with the desktop version since the version of 14.04 comes out. Frequently Used 3+ months **Docker**, Primarily used for different deep learning framework and CUDA version. Frequently Used 2+ years **VSCode**, Primarily used for Python dev, *.csv, *.json, *.md locally. Or, edit the remote file by ssh tunnel. **Familiar**

PROGRAMMING

3+ years Python, available for multi-tasks such as build-up the tools, scripts, and do analyze Familiar 1 year **RScript**, used to do simple data analysis and recommend system. Used 2 years **C++**, used in the course project in university. Used

RESEARCH

n year	Software , always follow up the new tech about design, tools, and architecture	Frequently Used
2+ year	Management , get interested since be involved in the server maintained.	Used
1+ year	Deep Learning , especially on detection and tracking (computer vision task).	Frequently Used
1 year	Data analysis , interested in finding the hidden value behind the data.	Used

Presentation

C.M. YANG · RÉSUMÉ JANUARY 19, 2019

BigData Center, Shih Hsin University

LECTURER FOR < PYTHON-CRAWLING-TUTORIAL>

Oct. 2018

Taipei, Taiwan

Dec. 2017, Jan. 2018

Aug. & Dec. 2017

- · GET/ POST crawling
- PTT Crawling
- Facebook Graph API Crawling

Al academy course Remote

LECTURER FOR < PYTHON-CRAWLING-TUTORIAL> Jun. 2018

- · Video recording
- GET/ POST/ File/ Website/ Selenium crawling
- · Facebook Graph API Crawling

Aletheia University Taipei, Taiwan

LECTURER FOR <PYTHON TUTORIAL>, <PYTHON-CRAWLING-TUTORIAL>

- · Python basic, Pandas
- · GET/ POST/ File/ Website crawling
- · Facebook Graph API Crawling

DataSci series course Academic Sinica, Taiwan

LECTURER FOR < PYTHON-CRAWLING-TUTORIAL>

- · File/ Website/ Selenium crawling
- Facebook Graph API Crawling
- · Anti-crawling

Writing

Tech write-up Medium

May. 2018 - PRESENT WRITER

• Personal tech write-up for all the field I interested in.

Makers' Open Lab for Innovation

blog.moli.rocks WRITER OF KNOWLEDGE-BASED SHARING SYSTEM Nov. 2016 - Sep. 2017

• Personal tech write-up for all the field I interested in.

Education

National Chi Nan University (NCNU)

Nantou, Taiwan Sep. 2015 - Jul. 2016

MASTER'S DEGREE IN COMPUTER SCIENCE AND INFORMATION ENGINEERING

• The Master research competition in the department. (First Prize)

• Paper "Integrated Sleep Scheduling for Multiple Relays and UEs in LTE-TDD"

Memorial University of Newfoundland (MUN)

St. John, NL, Canada Sep. 2014 - Apr. 2015

BACHELOR EXCHANGE STUDENT IN COMPUTER SCIENCE

• Two semesters with GPU 3.5, 3.6 respectively. • COMP 1710 - Object-Orient Program, COMP 2500 - Data Anlys with Script Language, COMP 3715 - Network Comp/ Web Application

• COMP 3719 - Theory of computation and algorithm, COMP 4759 - Computer Network

National Chi Nan University (NCNU)

Nantou, Taiwan

BACHELOR'S DEGREE IN COMPUTER SCIENCE AND INFORMATION ENGINEERING Sep. 2011 - Jun. 2015

• The Director of Student Association of CSIE Department.

C.M. YANG · RÉSUMÉ JANUARY 19, 2019